<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>_metapages on Vladimir Vakhter</title>
    <link>http://example.org/_metapage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in _metapages on Vladimir Vakhter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/_metapage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Achievements</title>
      <link>http://example.org/achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/achievements/</guid>
      <description>Scholarships Fulbright Graduate Student Program, USA ⦁ 2019 &amp;ndash; 2022 Selected among 35 participants from Russia based on leadership potential and academic achievements. The program awards about 8,000 students, scholars, and professionals from more than 160 countries yearly. Edmund S. Muskie Summer Internship Program, USA ⦁ 2020 Selected among 49 participants from Eastern Europe, Caucasus, and Central Asia based on global leadership and cross-cultural engagement. Sverdlovsk Region Governor&#39;s Scholarship, Russia ⦁ 2015 &amp;ndash; 2016 Selected among 36 graduate and postgraduate students at the Ural Federal University based on leadership potential, academic contributions, research achievements, and athletic performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://example.org/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/education/</guid>
      <description>Degrees MS in Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering @ Worcester Polytechnic Institute, USA ⦁ 2019 &amp;ndash; 2021 [Transcript] Focus: Verilog, VHDL, Computer Architecture, Design of Software Systems, Machine Learning, Blockchain &amp; Cryptocurrencies, Cryptography, System-level Design &amp; Modeling, and Research. Specialist* in Electronics &amp; Automation @ Ural Federal University, Russia ⦁ 2010 &amp;ndash; 2016 [Transcript] (*) = equivalent to BS/MS Thesis: Development of a Hardware-and-Software System for Magneto-optical Measurements. Focus: Electrical Engineering, Physics, Mathematics, Software Development, and Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://example.org/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/experience/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineering Research Assistant @ Worcester Polytechnic Institute, USA ⦁ Aug 2021 &amp;ndash; Present Description: Embedded programming for biomedical IoT devices. Coded in C. Signal Processing Intern @ Analog Devices, Inc., USA ⦁ May 2023 &amp;ndash; Aug 2023 Description: Assessment and development of a physical activity monitoring algorithm bundle for a wrist-worn wearable. Research Associate @ Worcester Polytechnic Institute, USA ⦁ Jun 2021 &amp;ndash; Jul 2022 Description: Developed a desktop application for communication with Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://example.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/publications/</guid>
      <description>Journals [Scholar] V. Vakhter, B. Kahraman, G. Bu, F. Foroozan, and U. Guler, &#34;A Prototype Wearable Device for Noninvasive Monitoring of Transcutaneous Oxygen&#34;, IEEE TBioCAS, early access, pp. 1 -12, Mar. 3, 2023. [Scholar] V. Vakhter, B. Soysal, P. Schaumont, and U. Guler, &#34;Threat Modeling and Risk Analysis for Miniaturized Wireless Biomedical Devices&#34;, IEEE Internet of Things, vol. 9, no. 15, pp. 13338-13352, Aug.1, 2022. [Scholar] A. Ishchenko, V. Vakhter, A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://example.org/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/resume/</guid>
      <description>My professional and educational backgrounds are summarized below.
View my resume View my coursework </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
